Guide to the Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
- Series II. Assignments
  - Sheets #16-19: General shots in and around Youth Building at State Fair, Aug.-Sept. 1986; 1186; 74 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #20: Gerald Kalk's daughter on bicycle on Cornell Plantations, Aug. 1986; 1186; 12 (Box 23)
  - Dairy Days award for 1986, Murray Elliot with William T. Underwood from Tully, NY and Melvin B. Empet from Freeville, NY, Jan. 1986; 1187; 11 (Box 23)
  - Campus Scenes, Sheet #1: Frames 1a-7a: Class/students near Plant Science Building inspecting plants; frames 8-14a: Materials being moved into Corson-Mudd Hall; Frames 14-20a: HE Nursery School/Children at play; Frames 14-19a: Class in Ag. Economics, 1984-1985; 1188; 26 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #2: People walking on Ag. Quad/ Sheet #3: Clock Tower & Lib. Slope, 1984-1985; 1188; 6 (Box 23)
  - Extension Conference to mark 75th Anniversary of Extension., Mar. 1987; 1189; 8 (Box 23)
  - Excellence Awards/Statler Inn, Jan. 1986; 1189; 280 (Box 23)
  - Albany--Human Ecology Symposium, Jan. 1986; 1190; 10 (Box 23)
  - Local Roads Program group shot, Nov. 1985; 1191; 7 (Box 23)
  - Media Services Activities, sheet #1: Radio Center Activities, Jan. 1986; 1192; 27 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #2: Roy Lonnberg working on graphics IV system at Exhibit Shop, Jan. 1986; 1192; 24 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #3: ETV crew recording musicians for TV spots on Nutrition, 1982; 1192; 28 (Box 23)
  - Sheets #4 & 5: ETV crew shooting "Soil Taxonomy" for Agronomy in Puerto Rico, June 1982; 1192; 76 (Box 23)
  - Display Photos for MVR Auditorium, Hallway, Field & Int. Study Prog., Admissions & Etc. in MVR, Sheet #1: Prof. Babcock/HSS, Jan. 1986; 1193; 30 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #2: Asst. Prof. Susan Hester/T & A, Feb. 1986; 1193; 17 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #3: Asst. Prof. Ed Kain/HDFS, Feb. 1986; 1193; 15 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #4: Ellen DeLara/HE Student Services, Feb. 1986; 1193; 6 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #5: Asso. Prof. Ron Beckman/ DEA, Aug. 1986; 1193; 10 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #6&7: Asst. Dean Charles McClintock, Sept. 1986; 1193; 15 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #8: Paul Chen/Former ID 408 student, Oct. 9, 1986; 1193; 7 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #9: Shannon Carney, Lorena Molina, Laura Szeliga, Oct. 9, 1986; 1193; 12 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #10: Marilyn Geizer--student in work situation at CG & S Services at Gannett Clinic--Supervisor Judy Borrill, Dec. 3, 1986; 1193; 8 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #11: Jung Jin Yoo--student in work situation at Tompkins County Human Rights Commission, Ithaca, NY (student in HSS), Dec. 9, 1986; 1193; 15 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #12: Howard Kibrick--HSS student at Groton High School counseling students, Dec. 11, 1986; 1193; 15 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #13: Nancy Potter--TC Agent and Roy Ives talking about Family Matters Program at WHCU Radio, Dec. 18, 1986; 1193; 24 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #14: Irving Lazarr with assistant doing research with computer and looking at printouts, Jan. 9, 1986; 1193; 25 (Box 23)
  - Sheets #15&16: Extension Service Inservice Program called Health Policy: Issues & Education Responses Workshop "Quality of Pre-natal Care" with Chris Olson and Laura Bitter giving the talk to agents, Jan. 22, 1987; 1193; 31 (Box 23)
  - Sheets #17&18: Frank Becker--Professor of DEA and William Sims Chair Professor looking at blueprints, Jan. 29, 1987; 1193; 41 (Box 23)
  - Sheets #19&20: Colin Campbell--Professor Nut. Bio. Chem/Nut. Sciences in lab and with research assistants, Jan. 27, 1987; 1193; 70 (Box 23)
  - Sheets #21&22: Keith Bryant-Professor CEH and Jennifer Gerner Associate Professor CEH in classroom portrait, Jan. 26, 1987; 1193; 31 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #23: General office shots of Lee C. Lee--Associate Prof. HDFS and Paul Lutwak at electron microscope in Bard Hall, Feb. 2, 1987; 1193; 17 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #24: Valerie King--HSS Social Work Program in HE interning Mental Health Association and Arlene Richardson--Support Group Clearing House Coord.--Mental Health. and Nancy Potter--Tompkins County agent with Nancy Perkins--Senior Program Assistant--Tomp. Co., Feb. 5, 1987; 1193; 18 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #25: Portrait of Nancy Potter--Tomp. Co. Coop. Ext. agent, Feb. 5. 1987; 1193; 4 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #26: Ceil Blumenstock--undergrad in HE working at Challenge Industries with Beverly Pala and Joey Reeve, Feb. 5, 1987; 1193; 14 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #27: Phyllis Moen--Associate Professor HDFS in her office, Feb. 5, 1987; 1193; 29 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #28: Students in classroom situation NG05 MVR, Feb. 11, 1987; 1193; 15 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #29: K.C. Carr--HE grad working at Tompkins County Mental Health Clinic, Feb. 12, 1987; 1193; 20 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #30: Kay Obendorf/Chairman & Professor T & A Dept., Feb. 19, 1987; 1193; 27 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #31: Participants in Family Matters Program at NE Elem. School (Nancy Potter), Mar. 11, 1987; 1193; 21 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #32&33: Martha Mapes--Extension Associate, Brenda Carpenter--Tompkins County 4-H Program Assistant and Kristen Hedlund--student at Ithaca High School working together in Conference Room. Comstock, Mar. 27, 1987; 1193; 38 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #34: Christianne Dean and Ellie Peavey working on materials for inservice, Apr. 1, 1987; 1193; 36 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #35: Marie Layer--Tompkins County with teens, Apr, 3, 1987; 1193; 34 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #36: Christianne Dean with inservice materials in conference room, Apr. 9, 1987; 1193; 37 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #37: Mon Cochran with Family Matters materials, Apr. 29, 1987; 1193; 14 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #38: Gail DeWeese/Assistant Professor TXA, Aug. 18, 1987; 1193; 7 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #39: Frames 1-10; Robert Greene/Counselor Student Services; Frames 11-18: Catherine Crawford/Assistant Prof. HSS, Aug. 18, 1987; 1193; 12 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #40: Ruth Bounows/Lecturer HSS & Field & International Studies, Aug. 18, 1987; 1193; 5 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #41: Nancy Carney/Assistant Dir. of Admissions, Aug. 20, 1987; 1193; 6 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #42: Jere Haas/Associate Professor in Nut. Sci doing research with grad student Heidi Kalkways, Feb. 29, 1988; 1193; 24 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #43: Steve Ceci--Associate Prof. HDFS in office with his daughter and another child at computer, Mar. 4, 1988; 1193; 18 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #44: Jeanne Hogarth/Assistant Professor CEH/office/lab shots, Mar. 7, 1988; 1193; 34 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #45: Paul Eshelman/Associate Professor DEA in his office, Mar. 11, 1988; 1193; 9 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #46: Ann Lemley/Associate Professor TXA, Mar. 4, 1988; 1193; 28 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #47: William Trochim/Associate Professor HSS at computer, Mar. 4, 1988; 1193; 18 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #48: Paul Eshelman/Associate Professor DEA in his office, Mar. 4, 1988; 1193; 15 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #49: Urie Brofenbrenner--Prof. Emeritus HDFS, A.D. White Prof. At Large, Jacob Gould Shurman Prof. & Psychology, Aug. 18, 1988; 1193; 11 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #50: Frames 1-10: Jean Robinson/Associate Dean HE, Aug. 18, 1988; 1193; 7 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #50: Frames 11-18: Robert Avery/Asso. Prof. CEH, Aug. 18, 1988; 5 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #51: William Putsis/Visiting Assistant Prof. CEH, Aug. 18, 1988; 1193; 6 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #52: Frames 26-31: Sam Beck/Senior Lecturer--New Director of Field & International Studies, Aug. 18, 1988; 1193; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #52: Frames 33-39: Rosemary Key/Assistant Prof. CEH, Aug. 19, 1988; 1193; 5 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #53: Frames 2-4: Rosemary Key/Assistant Prof. CEH, Aug. 19, 1988; 1193; 2 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #53: Frames 5-17: Susan Niezelski/Lecturer in TXA, Aug. 19, 1988; 1193; 8 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #54: Frames 20-38: Cindy Hazan/Assistant Prof. HDFS, Aug. 19, 1988; 1193; 12 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #55: Frames 1-9: Scott Maynes/Professor CEH, Sept. 1, 1988; 1193; 6 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #55: Frames 11-17: Loren Geistfield/Visiting Prof. in CEH, Sept. 1, 1988; 1193; 5 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #56: Frames 1-9: Steve Robertson/Asso. Prof. In HDFS, Sept. 1, 1988; 1193; 6 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #56: Frames 10-15: Patti Papapietro/Counselor in Student Services, Sept. 1, 1988; 1193; 4 (Box 23)
  - Sheets #57&58: Agents and faculty talking together/Charlotte Coffman doing presentation on protective clothing (color slides). Taken at the new Extension Office on Willow Ave. for use in the TXA Display, Nov. 1, 1986; 1193; 49 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #59: Frames 2-11: Katherine Boser, Jan. 25, 1989; 1193; 6 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #59: Frames 13-18: Lisa Hilbert, Jan. 25, 1989; 1193; 4 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #60: Scott Kenney, Jan. 25, 1989; 1193; 6 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #61: Frames 26-32: Mark Miller, Jan. 25, 1989; 1193; 5 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #61: Frames 35-5 Heidi Lipson (Do not use), Jan. 25, 1989; 1193; 6 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #62: Frames 34-3: Kristina Shneider, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 4 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #62: Frames 4-10: Carol Edwards, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 5 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #62: Frames 14-18: Linnae Sperling, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 3 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #63: Frames 3-8: Linnae Sperling, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 4 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #63: Frames 9-16: Rebecca Erdman, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 5 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #63: Frames 19-13: Gabriella Tayac, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 3 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #64: Frames 23-27: Beth Paciello, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 3 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #64: Frames 28-37: Susan Freund, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 6 (Box 23)
  - Sheet # 65: Frames 1-5: Susan Psaila, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 3 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #65: Frames 6-18: Betty Lee, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 9 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #66: Frames 3-12: Bethany Davis, Jan. 26, 1989; 1193; 6 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #67: Frames 1-16: Heidi Lipson, Feb. 16, 1989; 1193; 11 (Box 23)
  - Stone Hall Demolition, Sheets #1&2: Beginning demolition of Stone Hall, Feb. 10, 1986; 1194; 23 (Box 23)
  - Sheets #3-7: Demolition of Stone Hall, Dec. 1986; 1194; 41 (Box 23)
  - ETV Crew, Feb. 19, 1986; 1195; 25 (Box 23)
  - Bio Technology Activities for Annual Report and Newsletters, Sheet #1: Lab technicians/Bradfield Hall, Feb. 1986; 1196; 18 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #2: Lab technicians/Clark Hall working with lab equipment in Biophysics, Mar. 1986; 1196; 16 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #3: Ted Thannhauser and equipment--protein sequencer and amino acid analysis HPLC--taken in Olin labs 661 and 675, July 3, 1986; 1196; 22 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #4: Groundbreaking for new Biotechnology Building, June 27, 1986; 1196; 28 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #5: Tissue Culture Room in Bradfield Hall, Oct. 9, 1986; 1196; 7 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #6: Tissue Culture Room in Bradfield Hall in color with Elizabeth Earle, Oct. 9, 1986; 1196; 10 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #7: Biotechnology lab--Susan Combs. Melody Sweet--Frames 1-4; and Post Doc's Katherine Jansen and Churl Min--Frames 5-9, July 17, 1986; 1196; 9 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #8: Biotechnology Management Workshop, Oct. 20, 1986; 1196; 20 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #9: Biotechnology Symposium/Poster Session general candids, Oct. 21, 1986; 1196; 27 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #10: Joseph L. Goldstein and Michael S. Brown, co-recipients for their discovery of cell surface receptors for a plasma cholesterol transport protein, Oct. 22, 1986; 1196; 13 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #11: Carl Batt in Molecular Genetics Lab in Food Science, Jan. 8, 1987; 1196; 13 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #12: John Jachetta and Ray Wu in Molecular Genetics in Wing Hall, Jan. 9, 1987; 1196; 24 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #13: Lab shots with Robert Belly--Eastman Kokak Scientist and Thomas Fox--Associate Professor Genetics in lab at 202 Bradfield Hall, Feb. 18, 1987; 1196; 22 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #14: Lab scene with John Lis--Associate Prof. Bio Chem.--Molecular Cell Biology and Prof. Mariana Wolfner--Assistant Prof. Development Biology and Kevin Krause, Feb. 18, 1987; 1196; 23 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #15: Construction photos of new Biotechnology Building, Mar. 25, 1987; 1196; 11 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #16: Dr. Hammas at his desk in Baker Lab, Aug. 4, 1987; 1196; 8 (Box 23)
  - Sheets 17&18: Bio Tech Symposium--photos of Prof. Fersht speaking at podium and later with Dr. Hammas, Oct. 19, 1987; 1196; 46cn (Box 23)
  - Sheet #19: Mike Shuler' s grad student with Bioreactor (Chemical Eng.), Nov. 30, 1987; 1196; 5 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #20: Carl Batts in lab/graduate students/food science labs--taken for General Foods Coop. Brochure, Jan. 27, 1987; 1196; 14 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #21: Barbara Baird--Professor Bio Tech office shot, Mar. 28, 1988; 1196; 24 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #22: Portrait of Ray Snyder--Former Director of Bio Technology, Apr. 20, 1988; 1196; 11 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #23: Portrait of Gordon Hammas--Director of Bio Tech, professor of Chemistry and Biotechnology, Apr. 22, 1988; 1196; 7 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #24: Frames 18-26: Portrait of Richard McCarty--Director of Biotech; Frames 27-32: Milton Zaitlin--Associate Director of Bio. Tech./Prof of Plant Path, June 21, 1988; 1196; 11 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #25: Portrait of Margaret Arion--Executive Director of Bio. Tech., June 21, 1988; 1196; 9 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #26: Portrait of Maureen Hanson--Associate Director of Bio. Tech./Member of Scientific Adv. Board, June 21, 1988; 1196; 7 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #27: Moving day for Bio. Technology staff into new Bio. Tech. Building, Nov. 21, 1988; 1196; 17 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #28: Moving into Bio. Tech. Building, Jan. 27, 1989; 1196; 19 (Box 23)
  - Sheets #29-31: Particle gun photos and various lab scenes, Feb. 6, 1989; 1196; 15cn/8B & W (Box 23)
  - Sheet #32: Central Lab facilities in the new Bio. Tech. Bldg., Feb. 20, 1989; 1196; 14 (Box 23)
  - Sheets #33-35: Dedication and open house of new Bio. Tech. Building, May 15, 1989; 1196; 101 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #36: Todd Gusek in Food Science lab with equipment/sterilizing for microorganisms and transfer to plates, June 23, 1989; 1196; 9 (Box 23)
  - Food Science Faculty and Staff, Sheet #1: Marion Smithers, David K. Barbano, Maureen Chapman, Anne Donnelly, Tim Nock, Tom Burke, James Stouffer, Feb. 1986; 1197; 627 (entire job) (Box 23)
  - Sheet #2: Margaret Jacobs, Robert Radmussen, Robert Zall, Jenny Clark, Hope Bauch, Joe Hotchkiss, Jerry Brown, David Brown, Gary Senyk, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #3: J.M. Regenstein, Janene Gargiulo, Bill Anderson, Bruce German, D. Beerman, Z. Haque, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #4: Nancy King, Joanna Lynch, Fay Bower, Vikram Mistry, Larry Orton, Glenn Grossman, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #5: Dean Benware, Jim Cornell, Rick La Bumbard, K. Kassam, Shirley Kazlowski, Julie Schieb, Frank Liu, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #6: George Houghton, R.C. Baker, Pat Fleming, Alex Vecchio, Doug Rector, John Kinsella, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #7: Belur Lokesh, Joe Chen, Navin Kuma Kella, Edmund Leonard, Sookhee Ha, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #8: Karen Cramker, Yoshiro Kamata, Shin-ya Tanimoto, Don Lisk, Debbie Bennett, Robert S. Parker, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #9: Helen Wright, Syed S. H. Rizvi, June Inman, Marsha St. John, Lois Seymour, Bill Turk, Ed Vance, Tom Keagle, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #10: D.K. Bandler, Karen DeCuyke, Debra Johnson, D.C. Graham, Steve Cockram, Shirley Olds, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #11: Ruth Lindenthal, Dana Whithead, Frank Kosikowski, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #12: F. Kosikowski, Pirkko Antila, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #13: Janice Brown, Eugene Wolff, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #14: Terry Fowler, Feb. 1986; 1197; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - James Kuehl smoking while typing for use in "Smoking in the Workplace", Mar. 3. 1986; 1198; 10 (Box 23)
  - BTI Annual Report lab scenes and activities for BTI Annual Report, Jan. 1986; 1199; 278 (Box 23)
  - Nutrition Comes Alive Project # 222, Sheets #1-5: Children working on nutrition projects at Central School, Mar. 1986; 1200; 169 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #6: Northeast Elementary School students/Sue Warner's class, Apr. 1986; 1200; 10 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #7: Bomb Calorimeter, Apr. 1986; 1200; 9 (Box 23)
  - Students and faculty of HE for Search Mailer, Feb. 1986; 1201; 19 (Box 23)
  - New agents orientation (20 new agents), Mar. 1986; 1202; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheets #1&2: New Comstock Hall lab, library and insect collection, used for publicity purposes before the building dedication, Mar. 1986; 1203; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheets #4-8: Comstock Hall dedication and tours through facility, Speakers in Corson-Mudd and Statler Inn, May 2&3, 1986; 1203; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Rodney Dietert/Assistant Professor of Poultry and Avian Sciences. Taken for use in ICET Newsletter, Mar. 1986; 1204; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - In Depth Week photos for IAD, Mar. 1986; 1205; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Photos taken for Derwood Burns for publicity purposes, Sheet #1: Frames 27-32: Berndell "Del" G., Boss--Industrial Ext. Broome County; Frames 33-36a: Derwood Guy Berns--Extension Specialist Cooperative Extension, 1206; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #2: Herschel Blackburn/Cooperative Extension, Apr. 1986; 1206; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #3: Bob Kelchner/Extension Associate, Jan. 1986; 1206; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Bruce Bower/Cooperative Extension teaching a computer course for F & LSQ, Mar. 1986; 1207; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - 4-H Capital Days in Albany, NY, Mar. 1986; 1208; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Food and Life Sciences Quarterly, Sheets #1-3: Small Foods Labs (Private Companies) in Langmuir Lab and Peter Steponkus's lab in Bradfield Hall, Apr. 1986; 1209; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #4: Photos of students Donald Robin and Jacqueline Rejman from Southern Cayuga Central School to be used for article "Computers in the Classroom", July 24, 1986; 1209; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheets #5&6: Garbage cans along streets in Ithaca, NY, Aug. 13, 1986; 1209; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #7: Bath, NY street scene, Aug. 12, 1986; 1209; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #8: Frames 2-7: Groton, NY street scene; Frames 8-12: Farm for sale near Locke, NY on Rt. 38, Aug. 12, 1986; 1209; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #9: Color Transp. Groton NY and Farm for sale, Aug. 12, 1986; 1209; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheets #10&11: Bath, NY, Aug. 12, 1986; 1209; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Color prints of award recipients in Chemical Engineering, Apr. 1986; 1210; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Award recipients--LA students from Syracuse and Cornell, Apr. 1986; 1211; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - George McGovern and William F. Buckley debate in Bailey Hall, Apr. 24, 1986; 1212; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Minority Grad. Brochure photographs, Sheet #1: Carl Blake--grad student in Music Department, Apr. 1986; 1213; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #2: James Davis--grad student in HSS, Apr. 1986; 1213; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #3: Black Graduate Student Asso. Meeting candids & group, Apr. 1986; 1213; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #4: Jovita Thomas--grad student in Business School, Apr. 1986; 1213; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #5: Cassandra Smith--grad student in Law School, May 8, 1986; 1213; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #6: Pamela Blackshear--grad student/Vet School with horse, May 7, 1986; 1213; 13 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #7: Silvia Lopez--Chemistry, May 9, 1986; 1213; 25 (Box 23)
  - Sheet #8: Victor Morales--grad student in government, May 20, 1986; 1213; 6 (Box 23)
  - Scholarship/Donor Reception in Balch Hall, May 1986; 1214; 58 (Box 23)
  - Symposium--"Adolescent Development in West Germany and United states" with four German guests, Apr. 1986; 1215; 48 (Box 23)
  - Chemical Eng. Faculty and Mechanics Thermal Statistics Dynamics Group and dog, Apr. 1986; 1216; 12 (Box 23)
  - Ellen DeLara counseling family (false), Apr. 1986; 1217; 15 (Box 23)
  - Speech Contest (9 people), Apr. 1986; 1218; 6 (Box 23)
  - Landscapes--Cayuga Heights and West Hill, May 1986; 1219; 16 (Box 23)
  - Exteriors of Riley Robb and Rice Hall, Wing Hall, Vet Tower Animal Rooms, May 1986; 1220; 31 (Box 23)
  - Installation of Gamma Sigma Delta initiation and banquet Charter meeting, May 20, 1986; 1221; 87 (Box 23)
  - 75th Anniversary celebration "Partners in Extension" for Cooperative Extension, June 6-7, 1986; 1222; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Adirondack Fisheries, June 4, 1986; 1223; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - ALS News, Sheet #1: Senior Barbeque, May 30, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #2: Three generations Martin Rock and family, June 1, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheets #3&4: ALS Breakfast and reunion, June 14, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #5: Stephanie Major with models--replica of roadways about 8-9' long, Sept. 16, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheets #6-15: Outstanding Alumni Banquet and ALS Round-up, Sept. 19-20, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #16: Charles Smith/Director of Information Services Lab of Ornithology, Oct. 8, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #17-19: Photos of Red Angus Beef Cattle donated to Ag. College; also Black Angus and field corn and general farm shots, Sept. 23, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #20: Judy Nguyen/student, Oct. 30, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #21: Steve Saraydor at the Indian Longhouse on Cornell Plantations, Nov. 6, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #22: Pony Barn Open House--Equine Metabolism Unit, Mar. 3, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #23: Three students wearing Cornell alumni T-shirts, Mar. 12, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #24: ROTC Army Lt. Col. Buchwald and Captain Barrows in Barton Hall with recruits doing workouts, Mar. 11, 1986; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #25: Elizabeth Oltenacu/Associate Prof. An. Sci., Mar. 30, 1987; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #26: Larry Walker in lab (Bio Chem Lab) in Wing Hall, Apr. 1, 1987; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #27: Peter Steponkus using his Cryo microscope in his Bradfield Hall lab, Jan. 21, 1988; 1224; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Senior Reception at A.D. White House, May 28, 1986; 1225; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Highway School, June 11, 1986; 1226; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Two authors (Ken Purdy and Dan Decker) together for photo to be used in Wildlife Society Bulletin, June 11, 1986; 1227; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Frank Rhodes and Roger Wei--Recognition project presentation held in Uris Library Terrace outside, June 12, 1986; 1228; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #1-5: Group shot of participants in course of "Maternal Nutrition During Pregnancy", Sheet #2: Group shot, June 23, 1986; 1229; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - 4-H Foundation Annual Meeting, Luncheon and Presentations, July 1, 1986; 1230; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - HE Student Services staff members: Sheet #1: Joe Selden, 1231; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #2: Bobbie Morse, 1231; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #3: Kris DeLuca-Beach, Lynn Wiley, 1231; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #4: Vernon Lisbon, July 3, 1986; 1231; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #5: Lynn Wiley, July 29, 1986; 1231; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Stocking Hall/Groundbreaking for new addition, July 9, 1986; 1232; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - William Trochum/HSS in working environment in MVR, July 18, 1986; 1233; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Empire Farm Days, Sheet #1: Frames 1-3: Portrait of Dale Young/Cayuga Co. agent; Frames 4-36: Dairy Audit Team at Tri-Stahl Dairy Farms--Cayuga Co., July 15, 1986; 1234; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #2: Frames 1-9: Judy Wright/Cayuga Co. agent with farmer; Frames 10-12: Beth Walldorff/Madison Co. agent with farmer, July 15, 1986; 1234; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #3: Frames 1-3: Judy Wright/Cayuga Co.; Frames 14-24: Howard Bateman/Cayuga Co.; Frames 25-7: Beth Waldorff, July 15, 1986; 1234; No. of Negs: (Box 23)
  - Sheet #4: Color negs same as sheet #2, July 15, 1986; 1234; No. of Negs: (Box 23)